<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Kendree Chen</title>
		<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Kendree Chen</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>KTBYTE Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/ktbyte/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/ktbyte/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[KTBYTE is an online academy for computer science education. I contributed as both a frontend and backend designer and developer, focusing on user experience, responsive design, and server-side functionality.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="KTBYTE Website" src="/images/ktbyte1.png"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.ktbyte.com/">KTBYTE</a> is an online academy dedicated to teaching computer science to students of all ages. As both a frontend and backend designer and developer, I worked on improving the website’s user interface and experience, implementing responsive layouts, building server-side features, and collaborating with the team to deliver a modern, accessible platform for CS education.</p>
<p><strong>Role:</strong> Frontend &amp; Backend Designer/Developer<br>
<strong>Tech Stack:</strong> HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python</p>
<p>Key contributions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Designed and implemented new UI components for course pages and dashboards</li>
<li>Enhanced site responsiveness and accessibility</li>
<li>Built and maintained backend features for course management and user authentication</li>
<li>Collaborated with backend and frontend teams to integrate dynamic content and APIs</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Girl Up New England Coalition Official Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/girl-up/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/girl-up/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[I designed and created a new official website for the Girl Up New England Coalition, on which I am an executive board member. Girl Up is a United Nations foundation that seeks to empower young women in making change in the world. I have been a part of Girl Up for four years and currently serve on the STEM committee of the executive board of the New England Coalition of 90+ clubs.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Girl Up Website Thumbnail" src="/images/girlup.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Poseidon-Bot</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/poseidon-bot/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/poseidon-bot/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Poseidon-Bot is an AI chatbot that uses retrieval augmented generation (RAG) architecture to allow the model to specialize in documents uploaded by the user. This was a project I worked on as part of a summer internship with Boston University's SAIL Lab during the summer of 2024. I designed and developed the application end-to-end. The frontend was written in Flutter and the backend in Python (FASTApi). It used a PostgreSQL database and Llama LLM.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Poseidon Bot Thumbnail" src="/images/canva.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Greater Boston STEM Program Portal</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/gbstem-portal/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/gbstem-portal/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[The Greater Boston STEM Program is a non-profit organization that provides free online and in person classes for underserved students in STEM. I am the maintainer and developer of the Greater Boston STEM Program's student and admin portal, which hosts gbSTEM classes, tracks attendance, handles interviewing and class creation, and more.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="gbSTEM Portal Thumbnail" src="/images/gbstem-portal.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Greater Boston STEM Program Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/gbstem-website/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/gbstem-website/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[gbSTEM is a 100% volunteer-driven 501(c)(3) not-for-profit organization that provides free STEM enrichment courses to underrepresented students in STEM. Since its inception in 2020, gbSTEM has reached over 2000 students and 500 volunteer instructors. I am president and software developer at gbSTEM and I am the maintainer and designer of the website.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="gbSTEM Website Thumbnail" src="/images/gbstem-website.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>The Wild Thistle Productions Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/thistle-productions/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/thistle-productions/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[The Wild Thistle Productions podcast website is a commissioned  project written in NextJs. It uses the Spotify API to automatically update content. The website lists all episodes and shows from the podcast in a modular format. I designed and coded the website from scratch.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="The Wild Thistle Productions Thumbnail" src="/images/thistle-1.png">
<img alt="The Wild Thistle Productions Thumbnail" src="/images/thistle-2.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Finding Vulnerabilities in Mobile APIs</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/mobile-api-vulnerabilities/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/mobile-api-vulnerabilities/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[I led the development of a script for programmatically testing common broken access control vulnerabilities in mobile APIs. I led a team in writing up the findings and published a paper on ArXiv.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="ICSS Thumbnail" src="/images/icss.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Lobstah Bots Robotics Team Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/lobstahbots/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/lobstahbots/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[I co-led the creation of the official website of my FIRST Robotics Competition team, the Lobstah Bots. The website was written in NextJS.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Lobstahbots Website Thumbnail" src="/images/lobstahbots.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Passionfruit Kitchen Website</title>
			<link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/passionfruit-kitchen/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 23:48:29 -0400</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/passionfruit-kitchen/</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Passionfruit Kitchen is my online food blog, founded in 2021. The website is designed, coded, and maintained by me entirely in plain HTML and CSS.]]></description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Passionfruit Kitchen Thumbnail" src="/images/passionfruit.png"></p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
